(Penny:)No. Did you figure out what you're
gonna do about the two girls?
(Raj:)As a matter of fact, I did.
(Raj:)I've spent so many years
living in fear,
(Raj:)saying no to new experiences,
but from now on,
(Raj:)I'm gonna say yes.
Yes to love,
(Raj:)yes to adventure, yes to life.
Whatever it may be,
(Raj:)the answer's going to be yes.
(Howard:)He's gonna die alone, right?
(Penny:)-Yeah.
-Yes.
(Amy:)I'm proud of you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You know, I'm proud of me, too.
(Sheldon:)I've done all my research,
I conducted an informal poll,
(Sheldon:)and I've arrived
at the rock-solid certainty
(Sheldon:)I've made the right choice.
(Amy:)Well, that's got to be
a good feeling.
(Sheldon:)Oh, it is.
(Sheldon:)-Although--
-Oh, crap.
(Sheldon:)I had the same feeling when
I made my dad buy a Betamax
(Sheldon:)instead of a VHS.
(Amy:)You were just a little kid.
(Amy:)A little kid
who picked the wrong format
(Sheldon:)to record The MacNeil/Lehrer Report
(Sheldon:)I also was certain that HD DVD
would win out over Blu-ray.
(Amy:)-How old were you then?
-Old enough to know better.